

# ADAM POMPOSELLI Freelancer

# **PRESENTATION**

I've been developing for 5 years in many industries, such as the web, video games, blockchain, testing, and embedded programming. Working with such a variety of technologies forced me to work with many programming languages such as C, C++, C#, Javascript, Typescript, Java, PHP, etc. This engrained not only programming principles but engineering concepts that I profit from in my day-to-day work. I am open to any new challenge and I can adapt really fast due to my really versatile experience.

To summarise, I worked in game development for 4 years. In parallel, I learned full-stack web development and blockchain development for 2 years. I then started my graduate studies at ESGI and had to find a job in IT to validate my semester. I applied for a web developer position but ended up working as a QA Automation Tester for 6 months.

#### CONTACT B

- difallahadam2003@gmail.com
- www.apz-dev.me

# **HARD SKILLS**

- React (Typescript)
- Game Developement (Unity/C#)
- Selenium (WebDriver)
- UX/UI (Figma, Adobe XD)
- Cypress



### **EXPERIENCE**

### Freelance Web Developer - Agence ZED

May 2022 - June 2022 · 2 Months

- · Mainly worked with WordPress and many popular plugins such as Divi, WPML, ACF, and others.
- Create the user interface using Divi and based on the designer's mockups for the website.
- Migrate the preproduction website to the live website's web server.
- Using WPML and in collaboration with a freelance translator, implement a multilingual feature across the entire website.
- Setup and management of a business email with OVH.
- Newsletter subscription and management with MailChimp
- Development of a back-office for the product owner, allowing him to add content to his website without the need for developer intervention.

#### QA Tester - Equativ (formerly Smart)

Movember 2021 - April 2022 · 6 Months

- Collaborated with four software development engineers to understand the features and architecture of their multiple web-based applications so that they could be tested 100% efficiency.
- Improve the documentation of the QA process and provide daily status reports to the development team to reduce the likelihood of bugs and performance issues.
- · Assisting in all aspects of product testing, including test plan development, functional and technical design specifications definition, automation (Cypress, Selenium), execution, and delivery of well-tested solutions within tight deadlines.
- Keep project-related websites up to date (web development).

#### Freelance Web Developer & Blockchain Developer

June 2021 - July 2021 · 1 Month

- NextJs, styled-components, and Material UI were used to create a single-page web application.
- Using Web3js to handle both the application's communication with blockchain (Ethereum) and blockchain transactions (MetaMask) to purchase NFTs.
- Development and deployment of the project's smart contract using Solidity and Hardhat
- Smart Contract debugging and testing with Hardhat and Chai testing library

#### Technical skills

- QA Testing Methodologies : Blackbox, Troubleshooting, Performance Testing, Smoke, Acceptance, Regression, Exploratory
- Libraries & Frameworks: Cypress, Selenium, Appium,

React-testing-library, Chai, Mocha · Atlassian products: Jira, Bitbucket Versionning Tools : Git, SourceTree

• Database work: SQL



### **EDUCATION**

- Graduate Studies | ESGI École Supérieure de Génie Informatique Completed First Year
- Baccalaureate | Lycée Louis le Grand (Paris 5) BAC STI2D option SIN (With Highest Honour)



### **LANGUAGES**



FRANÇAIS, NATIVE



**ENGLISH, OPERATIONAL** 

ITALIANO, BEGINNER